<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="selfDoubt">

        <item>To succeed in life, you need two things. ignorance and confidence</item>
        <item>Believe in yourself, Have faith in your abilities. Without a humble but reasonable confidence in your own powers you cannot be successful or happy</item>
        <item>Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence</item>
        <item>We gain strength, and courage, and confidence by each experience in which we really stop to look fear in the face, we must do that which we think we cannot</item>
        <item>Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love</item>
        <item>When you have confidence, you can have a lot of fun. And when you have fun, you can do amazing things</item>
        <item>When a team outgrows individual performance and learns team confidence, excellence becomes a reality</item>
        <item>With confidence, you have won before you have started</item>
        <item>Inaction breeds doubt and fear. Action breeds confidence and courage. If you want to conquer fear, do not sit home and think about it. Go out and get busy</item>
        <item>If you have no confidence in self, you are twice defeated in the race of life</item>
        <item>Be courteous to all, but intimate with few, and let those few be well tried before you give them your confidence</item>
        <item>Confidence thrives on honesty, on honor, on the sacredness of obligations, on faithful protection and on unselfish performance. Without them it cannot live</item>
        <item>Confidence comes from discipline and training.</item>
        <item>You just have to be yourself and go full with confidence and be courageous</item>
        <item>Honor bespeaks worth. Confidence begets trust. Service brings satisfaction. Cooperation proves the quality of leadership</item>
        <item>Faith is a living, daring confidence in Gods grace, so sure and certain that a man could stake his life on it a thousand times</item>
        <item>In fact, the confidence of the people is worth more than money</item>
        <item>My style has changed and evolved mainly because I have grown to have more confidence in myself
        </item>
        <item>It is best to act with confidence, no matter how little right you have to it</item>
        <item>Great leaders do not need to act tough. Their confidence and humility serve to underscore their toughness</item>
        <item>The circulation of confidence is better than the circulation of money</item>
        <item>If you are presenting yourself with confidence, you can pull off pretty much anything</item>
        <item>Health is the greatest possession. Contentment is the greatest treasure. Confidence is the greatest friend. Non-being is the greatest joy</item>
        <item>Power without a nations confidence is nothing</item>
        <item>Working with great people makes you great; you learn a lot and it also gives you the experience and confidence to move on with your own career</item>
        <item>Being glamorous is about strength and confidence. It is black and white - dramatic. You have to be strong</item>
        <item>My confidence is easy to shake. I am very well aware of all of my flaws. I am aware of all the insecurities that I have</item>
        <item>Confidence does not come out of nowhere. It is a result of something, hours and days and weeks and years of constant work and dedication</item>
        <item>When you have police officers who abuse citizens, you erode public confidence in law enforcement. That makes the job of good police officers unsafe</item>
        <item>When you give a lot of confidence in people and you do not get it back, you are a bit disappointed, but its life</item>
        <item>Style is whatever you want to do, if you can do it with confidence</item>
        <item>Greed is the lack of confidence of ones own ability to create</item>
        <item>The trust of the people in the leaders reflects the confidence of the leaders in the people
        </item>
        <item>Leadership is a matter of having people look at you and gain confidence, seeing how you react If you are in control, they are in control</item>
        <item>Censorship reflects a societies lack of confidence in itself</item>
        <item>Whatever we expect with confidence becomes our own self-fulfilling prophecy</item>
        <item>Peace is not an absence of war, it is a virtue, a state of mind, a disposition for benevolence, confidence, justice</item>
        <item>If once you forfeit the confidence of your fellow-citizens, you can never regain their respect and esteem</item>
        <item>Honesty is the cornerstone of all success, without which confidence and ability to perform shall cease to exist</item>
        <item>The qualities I most admire in women are confidence and kindness</item>
        <item>There is no worse screen to block out the Spirit than confidence in our own intelligence
        </item>
        <item>It is not so much our friends help that helps us, as the confidence of their help.</item>
        <item>If you have no confidence in self, you are twice defeated in the race of life. With confidence, you have won even before you have started</item>
        <item>All you need is ignorance and confidence and the success is sure</item>
        <item>Confidence isnt optimism or pessimism, and its not a character attribute. Its the expectation of a positive outcome</item>
        <item>The unutterable violence of the Holocaust shook our confidence in the possibility of telling any story of faith at all</item>
        <item>I love the confidence that makeup gives me</item>
        <item>As a young boy, scouting gave me a confidence and camaraderie that is hard to find in modern life</item>
        <item>I tremble for my country when I hear of confidence expressed in me. I know too well my weakness, that our only hope is in God</item>
        <item>I think the best way to have confidence is not to allow everyone elses insecurities to be your own</item>
        <item>Whether you come from a council estate or a country estate, your success will be determined by your own confidence and fortitude</item>
        <item>Fighters display two things. They display confidence, or they display a look that says, I am not sure</item>
        <item>Doubt can motivate you, so do not be afraid of it. Confidence and doubt are at two ends of the scale, and you need both. They balance each other out</item>
        <item>Confidence is the most important single factor in this game, and no matter how great your natural talent, there is only one way to obtain and sustain it. work</item>
        <item>If you improve a teachers self-esteem, confidence, communication skills or stress levels, you improve that teachers overall effectiveness across the curriculum</item>
        <item>It is only prudent never to place complete confidence in that by which we have even once been deceived</item>
        <item>The man of genius inspires us with a boundless confidence in our own powers</item>
        <item>Confidence in the goodness of another is good proof of ones own goodness</item>
        <item>There is a difference between conceit and confidence. Conceit is bragging about yourself. Confidence means you believe you can get the job done</item>
        <item>Faith is deliberate confidence in the character of God whose ways you may not understand at the time</item>
        <item>The greater the artist, the greater the doubt. Perfect confidence is granted to the less talented as a consolation prize</item>
        <item>Your teammates give you the confidence. They give me the confidence all year, all postseason
        </item>
        <item>I think the most important thing about coaching is that you have to have a sense of confidence about what you are doing</item>
        <item>I do not have the confidence to pull off a moustache</item>
        <item>I think it takes a lot of confidence to be comfortable in being vulnerable</item>
        <item>Girl power is about loving yourself and having confidence and strength from within, so even if you are not wearing a sexy outfit, you feel sexy</item>
        <item>Confidence comes from hours and days and weeks and years of constant work and dedication
        </item>
        <item>Confidence is contagious. So is lack of confidence</item>
        <item>Analysis gave me great freedom of emotions and fantastic confidence. I felt I had served my time as a puppet</item>
        <item>Confidence. If you have it, you can make anything look good</item>
        <item>Besides pride, loyalty, discipline, heart, and mind, confidence is the key to all the locks
        </item>
        <item>Kids made fun of me because I was a slow learner, because I was hyperactive, because of a lot of things. Running gave me confidence</item>
        <item>Confidence is very sexy. You could be not cute at all and have such confidence</item>
        <item>Only one man ever betrayed my confidence, and that only in a minor matter</item>
        <item>I do not even know how to speak up for myself, because I do not really have a father who would give me the confidence or advice</item>
        <item>To walk around with an ego is a bad thing. To have confidence in yourself is a great thing
        </item>
        <item>Confidence is that feeling by which the mind embarks in great and honorable courses with a sure hope and trust in itself</item>
        <item>Confidence in others honesty is no light testimony of ones own integrity</item>
        <item>Confidence comes with maturity, being more accepting of yourself</item>
        <item>Courage is a mean with regard to fear and confidence</item>
        <item>When you win, you do not get carried away. But if you go step by step, with confidence, you can go far</item>
        <item>Confidence and a good sense of humor can usually win a chick over</item>
        <item>Conceit is bragging about yourself. Confidence means you believe you can get the job done
        </item>
        <item>You have to have confidence in your ability, and then be tough enough to follow through
        </item>
        <item>I know what it is like to feel that fear and the need of affirmation and appreciation. To build confidence in yourself is the toughest thing</item>
        <item>It hass been a dream of mine to run my own summer camp. I went to one as a kid, and I put on productions, and got lots of confidence</item>
        <item>The only thing that I can do is know that I have great confidence in raising children and being a great mother</item>
        <item>Coaches can teach you two things, confidence and technique</item>
        <item>We do not so much need the help of our friends as the confidence of their help in need</item>
        <item>He who closes his ears to the views of others shows little confidence in the integrity of his own views</item>
        <item>Most of the confidence which I appear to feel, especially when influenced by noon wine, is only a pretense</item>
        <item>I was always looking outside myself for strength and confidence but it comes from within. It is there all the time</item>
        <item>You need to play with supreme confidence, or else you will lose again, and then losing becomes a habit</item>
        <item>I have always had confidence. It came because I have lots of initiative. I wanted to make something of myself</item>
        <item>Confidence is a lot of this game or any game. If you do not think you can, you wont</item>
        <item>I want to thank my parents for somehow raising me to have confidence that is disproportionate with my looks and abilities</item>
        <item>I think confidence is the sexiest thing to have</item>
        <item>My confidence comes from the daily grind - training my butt off day in and day out.</item>
        <item>If you have money and you have fame, but you do not have any confidence in your blackness, then it is all for nothing</item>
        <item>I am always impressed by confidence, kindness and a sense of humour</item>
        <item>Confidence is everything in this business</item>
        <item>Confidence is a very fragile thing</item>
        <item>Golf is a matter of confidence. If you think you cannot do it, there is no chance you will
        </item>
        <item>Confidence is a plant of slow growth in an aged heart</item>
        <item>I have two bowls of confidence for breakfast each morning</item>
        <item>I am a combination between extreme insecurity and extreme confidence</item>
        <item>Confidence contributes more to conversation than wit</item>
        <item>As is our confidence, so is our capacity</item>
        <item>Confidence cannot find a place wherein to rest in safety</item>
        <item>Confidence is something you are born with. I know I had loads of it even at the age of 15
        </item>
        <item>Confidence is key. Sometimes, you need to look like you are confident even when you are not
        </item>
        <item>I have had confidence in myself all along. It was just a matter of getting the pieces back in place</item>
        <item>Religion is the possibility of the removal of every ground of confidence except confidence in God alone</item>
        <item>I am consumed with the fear of failing. Reaching deep down and finding confidence has made all my dreams come true</item>
        <item>I have confidence that we can form this kind of national community</item>
        <item>I did not have any confidence in my beauty when I was young. I felt like a character actress, and I still do</item>
        <item>Being successful at a very young age gave me the confidence and the capability to try out other things</item>
        <item>Art helped give me confidence</item>
        <item>Just be confident. I think confidence is the most attractive part of a person</item>
        <item>Concentration comes out of a combination of confidence and hunger</item>



    </string-array>
</resources>