<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quote2">
        <item>The difference between stumbling blocks and stepping stones is how you use them</item>
        <item>If someone tells you, You cannot they really mean, I cannot</item>
        <item>Whatever you want to do, do it now. There are only so many tomorrows</item>
        <item>When I do good, I feel good. When I do bad, I feel bad. That’s my religion</item>
        <item>The difference in winning and losing is most often not quitting</item>
        <item>You are never too old to set another goal or dream a new dream</item>
        <item>All things are difficult before they are easy</item>
        <item>Success is falling nine times and getting up ten</item>
        <item>Happiness, like unhappiness, is a proactive choice</item>
        <item>When the world pushes you to your knees, you’re in the perfect position to pray</item>
        <item>If you can change your mind, you can change your life</item>
        <item>Happiness often sneaks in through a door you didn’t know you left open</item>
        <item>The best way to gain self-confidence is to do what you are afraid to do</item>
        <item>Minds are like flowers, they only open when the time is right</item>
        <item>Sometimes when you lose your way, you find YOURSELF</item>
        <item>You do not have to be good at something to be liked</item>
        <item>No matter whether you believe in luck or chance, the final decision is from yourself</item>
        <item>Thoughts Become Things,Choose The Good Ones</item>
        <item>Never run from the enemy, tackle them</item>
        <item>Inaction creates nothing. Action creates success</item>
        <item>Believing in negative thoughts is the single greatest obstruction to success</item>
        <item>Poverty: a temporary financial low, curable by money</item>
        <item>Think big thoughts but relish small pleasures</item>
        <item>Success does not come to you; you go to it</item>
        <item>A person today who seems to have a great sense of self-esteem has his or her childhood days to thank for it</item>
        <item>You willed yourself to where you are today, so will yourself out of it</item>
        <item>What we perceive about ourselves is greatly a reflection of how we will end up living our lives</item>
        <item>A barrier is a limitation only when you perceive it as one</item>
        <item>If you say you can or you cannot you are right either way</item>
        <item>Positive energy is attracted to positive energy</item>
        <item>The failure to think positively can weigh on a cancer patient like a second disease</item>
        <item>If practice makes you perfect should not good behavior be added to the curriculum</item>
        <item>Flexibility requires an open mind and a welcoming of new alternatives</item>
        <item>The goal is to learn to be nurturing with yourself so you can feel free</item>
        <item>Flexibility requires an open mind and a welcoming of new alternatives</item>
        <item>The goal is to learn to be nurturing with yourself so you can feel free</item>
        <item>The truth is that you are innately good, wise, and powerful. You were created in and for good
        </item>
        <item>Every goal first started as something in our mind. You have it all within you</item>
        <item>Beliefs that are good promote your potential and enhance your unique special qualities</item>
        <item>Doctor, I appreciate your diagnosis, but I will not accept your verdict</item>
        <item>The mind is the mine of man, wherein he digs out good or evil</item>
        <item>Catch sunbeams in a mirror. A reflection of a sunbeam can melt an iceberg</item>
        <item>Well, if it can be thought, it can be done, a problem can be overcome</item>
        <item>Accept yourself: flaws, quirks, talents, secret thoughts, all of it, and experience true liberation
        </item>
        <item>Create your best life with your consciously chosen thoughts, words, and actions</item>
        <item>Do not be victim of life-negative religions. Be respectful to life, love and beauty</item>
        <item>Be your own hero. Be smart</item>
        <item>A positive attitude influences our behavior and dictates a successful approach</item>
        <item>Imagination is a timeless possibilities.You attract to you what you have always imagine</item>
        <item>Real life is the days we are going to live, not the days we lived</item>
        <item>Sometimes you literally need some pressure on your shoulder, to fetch the best in you</item>
        <item>Whatever you do keep moving forward</item>
        <item>Ambition is like a plague that can only be cured by success</item>
        <item>Nothing is hurt unless you are negative thinker</item>
        <item>Revolution starts within our own heart, not on the street</item>
        <item>When you are in a fix, often the fix is in you</item>
        <item>Surround yourself with positive people</item>
        <item>We must be willing to expand the heart in order to be able to expand our thinking</item>
        <item>Hope makes the dream a possibility</item>
        <item>Success is a state of mind. Think great and you will be great</item>
        <item>Positive thinking, daring life</item>
        <item>Look forward with confidence and backwards with attitude</item>
        <item>A gratitude prayer a day keeps stinkin thinkin away</item>
        <item>Master the mind with positive thoughts and affirmations</item>
        <item>Whatever you do,keep moving forward</item>
        <item>Purpose is to touch the life and hearts of others without stepping on others</item>
        <item>The mindset you have, determines the next step you take</item>
        <item>You can make a living by passing others up, you’ll make a killing by helping others up</item>
        <item>The only tension that gets my attention, is when I stick a fork too close to my silver filling</item>
        <item>Make yourself feel good. Be enthusiastic about your day</item>
        <item>Life is a gift, aim for the sky</item>
        <item>You can go as far as you think, imagine and dream. Anything is possible</item>
        <item>Courage is being who you are.Courage is sacred of thyself</item>
        <item>I dwell on endless possibilities</item>
        <item>Pursue great things.You are destiny for greatness</item>
        <item>Our thoughts create our future</item>
        <item>A gratitude prayer a day keeps stinkin thinkin away</item>
        <item>From yearning and wanting to grace and gratitude is a simple shift in belief and attitude
        </item>
        <item>You can make a living by passing others up, you’ll make a killing by helping others up
        </item>
        <item>Be positive. Be true. Be kind</item>
        <item>I dwell on great thoughts</item>
        <item>Good things happen in your life when you surround yourself with positive people</item>
        <item>Purpose is to touch the life and hearts of others without stepping on others</item>
        <item>Dare to dwell on great thoughts, you will be great</item>
        <item>Find your path, Live your journey, Transform your Life</item>
        <item>Sitting around fools increases your tolerance</item>
        <item>Mind is a flexible mirror, adjust it, to see a better world</item>
        <item>Maybe being broken helps you become a better person</item>
        <item>Each day has the potential of being your best day. You decide what each day will bring
        </item>
        <item>All roads out of hell lead home</item>
        <item>Never say anything about yourself you do not want to come true</item>
        <item>To change your life, you need to become aware of yourself</item>
        <item>Focus on what you can do right now, not what you cannot do right now</item>
        <item>If you are opportunist, then you are already one step closer to achieve your target</item>
        <item>I am a glass of Positivity; If you drink it,you will always find positives in you</item>
        <item>AIM BIG,THINK DEEP,WORK HARD,YOU WIN</item>
        <item>Be Positive. Be Passionate. Be Persistent. Be Poetic</item>
        <item>Some positive thinkers get consistent powerful results almost deserving of a scientific formula</item>
        <item>Being powerful means shifting our minds away from our troubles and into solution-thinking
        </item>
        <item>There is no reason to worry I started brand new story</item>
        <item>Never say anything about yourself you do not want to come true</item>
        <item>Change the way you think and you will change the way you feel</item>
        <item>You will be surrounded by negativity but you shall overcome it with positivity</item>
        <item>As architect of your reality, you are empowered to create it as you choose</item>
        <item>Gratitude is more of a compliment to yourself than someone else</item>
        <item>Always look at the positive side of life</item>
        <item>Think positively.Always focus on the positive side of any situation</item>
        <item>Flow with the go</item>
        <item>Daily love and kindness are the path to a happy life</item>
        <item>A kind thought, word, or action creates infinite ripples of caring, consideration, and peace
        </item>
        <item>Sometimes being happy takes effort. Invest time and energy in yourself and your happiness
        </item>
        <item>i never give up, i will try and try when my goal reaches</item>
        <item>When the positive mind takes the lead, the legs are safe to follow without any shaking
        </item>
        <item>When your bright future, becomes a dull regret of the past, take a deep breath and move on
        </item>
        <item>You can do anything you set your mind to</item>
        <item>There is no truth beyond perception. How you look at things is the truth for you</item>
        <item>An affirmation opens the door. It’s a beginning point on the path to change</item>
        <item>Constant repetition carries conviction</item>
        <item>Affirmation without discipline is the beginning of delusion</item>
        <item>I figured that if I said it enough, I would convince the world that I really was the greatest</item>
        <item>Belief consists in accepting the affirmations of the soul; unbelief, in denying them
        </item>
        <item>You become what you think about most of the time</item>
        <item>Every action and feeling is preceded by a thought</item>
        <item>The ancestor of every action is a thought</item>
        <item>As a man thinks in his heart, so is he</item>



    </string-array>
</resources>