<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="selfConf">


        <item>I accept peace within myself</item>
        <item>I am open and receptive to all the Universe has to offer me without limits, restrictions
        </item>
        <item>If you continuously compete with others, you become bitter. If you continuously compete with yourself, you become better</item>
        <item>It is not who you are that holds you back, it is who you think you are not</item>
        <item>You were given this life because you were strong enough to live it</item>
        <item>Do not worry if you have built your castles in the air. Now put the foundations under them
        </item>
        <item>When I breath, I inhale confidence and exhale timidity</item>
        <item>I love meeting strangers and approach them with boldness and enthusiasm</item>
        <item>I approve of myself and love myself deeply and completely</item>
        <item>I live in the present and am confident of the future</item>

        <item>My personality exudes confidence. I am bold and outgoing</item>
        <item>I am self-reliant, creative and persistent in whatever I do</item>
        <item>I am energetic and enthusiastic. Confidence is my second nature</item>
        <item>I always attract only the best of circumstances and the best positive people in my life</item>
        <item>I am a problem solver. I focus on solutions and always find the best solution</item>
        <item>I love change and easily adjust myself to new situations</item>
        <item>I love challenges. They bring out the best in me</item>
        <item>I am well groomed, healthy and full of confidence. My outer well being is matched by my inner well being</item>
        <item>Self confidence is what I thrive on. Nothing is impossible and life is great</item>
        <item>I always see only the good in others. I attract only positive people</item>

        <item>I face difficult situations with courage and conviction. I always find a way out of such situations</item>
        <item>Confidence comes naturally to me</item>
        <item>I am naturally confident</item>
        <item>I have unbreakable confidence within myself</item>
        <item>My confidence commands respect and attention</item>
        <item>I enjoy being confident and outgoing in social situations</item>
        <item>I impress others with my confident assertiveness</item>
        <item>Confidence empowers me to take action and live life to the fullest</item>
        <item>When I see something I want, I just go for it without hesitation</item>
        <item>Developing confidence will improve my life</item>

        <item>Feeling confident, assured, and strong is a normal part of my every day life</item>
        <item>I will succeed</item>
        <item>I will always love and respect myself</item>
        <item>My self esteem is growing</item>
        <item>Each day I believe in myself more and more</item>
        <item>My self image is starting to improve</item>
        <item>I will always think positively about myself</item>
        <item>I will achieve whatever I put my mind to</item>
        <item>I am starting to feel more confident in myself</item>
        <item>I am transforming into someone who is happy and positive</item>

        <item>I am  wise and adventurous</item>
        <item>I am overflowing with energy. </item>
        <item>There is abundant opportunities waiting for me. </item>
        <item>I am committed to my goals.  </item>
        <item>I walk tall. </item>
        <item>I work with abundant enthusiasm. </item>
        <item>I am a successful businessperson operating a thriving business. </item>
        <item>My body is achieving peak condition. </item>
        <item>My life overflows with wealth. </item>
        <item>I respect and accept myself.</item>

        <item>I live with joy and commitment.</item>
        <item>I recognise the power of my thoughts.</item>
        <item>I love using the power of choice.</item>
        <item>I face my fears and learn from them.</item>
        <item>Mistakes are my apprenticeships.</item>
        <item>I follow my inner drum beat.</item>
        <item>I use my time wisely.</item>
        <item>My life is an exciting adventure.</item>
        <item>Each day I learn more about how to achieve my goals.</item>
        <item>There is enough time for everything I need.</item>

        <item>I act with courage and confidence.</item>
        <item>I love and nurture myself. </item>
        <item>I take action that moves me forward. </item>
        <item>I willingly explore the unknown. </item>
        <item>I expand my familiar world by tapping the unfamiliar. </item>
        <item>I seek clarity. </item>
        <item>Centred and powerful, I live my values.  </item>
        <item>I am more than I am demonstrating. </item>
        <item>I choose to think only the best thoughts. </item>
        <item>I know there are magnificent possibilities within myself.</item>

        <item>I believe in me. </item>
        <item>I am wonderfully healthy. </item>
        <item>I choose to be the best that I can be.</item>
        <item>I welcome positive, new ideas.</item>
        <item>I feed my conscious mind with positive, inspiring words. </item>
        <item>I prepare thoroughly for things that matter. </item>
        <item>I deserve to achieve my goals. </item>
        <item>I focus on the good aspects of every person, place and thing. </item>
        <item>I look for the good that can come from a situation.</item>
        <item>I am responsible for who I am. </item>
        <item>I take great care of my body. </item>
        <item>I value my physical activity time. </item>
        <item>I am a doer-I love taking action.</item>
        <item>I have faith in my own opinions and make up my own mind. </item>
        <item>I have good ideas and make useful contributions. </item>
        <item>I have complete faith that I  will achieve my goals.</item>



    </string-array>
</resources>